{
    "subject": "resource/Ike_Turner",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/surname",
    "object": "Turner",
    "human_readable": "The surname of Ike Turner is Turner.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9841657876968384,
            "question": "What is the surname of Ike Turner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8564926385879517,
            "question": "Is 'Turner' a common surname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7009380459785461,
            "question": "Can you name a musician with the last name Turner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6673057675361633,
            "question": "Are there any famous people with the last name Turner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6265500783920288,
            "question": "What was the name of Ike Turner's most famous band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5553935170173645,
            "question": "Who were some of Ike Turner's collaborators?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4367624819278717,
            "question": "What musical instruments did Ike Turner play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40257886052131653,
            "question": "What genre of music is Ike Turner known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3770420551300049,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Ike Turner's personal life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2821270525455475,
            "question": "When was Ike Turner most active in the music industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The surname of Ike Turner is Turner.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5834_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Ike Turner's personal life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5834_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is Ike Turner known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5834_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What musical instruments did Ike Turner play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5834_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5834_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5834_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5834_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5834_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5834_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5834_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5834_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5834_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5834_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5834_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Ike Turner, including his full name being \"Ike Wister Turner,\" which confirms that the surname of Ike Turner is indeed \"Turner.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The surname of Ike Turner is actually registered as \"Wister\" and later as \"Ike Wister Turner\", not just \"Turner\".",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}